<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Upgrades>
    <Upgrade>
        <name>Fundamental Skin Science</name>
        <flavor>
            The skin of any organism can be transmuted into bronze by soaking it with water and then wringing it in a 41-43 degrees celcius
            enviromnent for 399 seconds.<![CDATA[<br/>]]><![CDATA[<br/>]]>
            +1 Bronze for every kill, even the idle kills
        </flavor>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
        <name>Blood Spear Fishing</name>
        <flavor>
            Out of the approximately 2791741.5 species of fish (Yes... there are several half-fishes), thousands of them are attracted
            to blood. Blood is good bait but it can be dangerous to have carnivorous animals know where you are.
            Blood Spear Fishing' is like a fishing-martial-art that makes using Blood safe in fishing. <![CDATA[<br/>]]><![CDATA[<br/>]]>
            Doubles Spearman Idle Revenue
        </flavor>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
        <name>Whetfish Ichthyology</name>
        <flavor>
            The Whetfish is a very common species, many can find it... few can use it. The magical scales and saliva of the fish can either
            harden solids or empower other magical sources. As you can already tell it is used to make weapons stronger
            ,hence its name which is derived from the 'whetstone' (And yes... the picture in the icon is an annotated
            Diagram of the fish). <![CDATA[<br/>]]><![CDATA[<br/>]]>
            +1 Attack for all Weapons
        </flavor>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
        <name>Blood Spear Fishing II</name>
        <flavor>
            More training means more skill, more skill allows more blood, more blood means more fish. <![CDATA[<br/>]]><![CDATA[<br/>]]>
            Doubles Spearman Idle Revenue
        </flavor>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
        <name>Swordsman Tracking</name>
        <flavor>
            Unlike Knights, Generic Swordsman are not trained how to track game. They are instead trained for armed combat. Coming from mediocre
            comes with the restriction of only having the liberty of learning one trade. In this case direct combat. <![CDATA[<br/>]]><![CDATA[<br/>]]>
            Doubles Swordsman Idle Revenue
        </flavor>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
        <name>Early Desensitization</name>
        <flavor>
            Knights are inherently sensitive to killing innocent creatures, this blatantly pointless world view prevents them from reaching
            their full hunting potential. A decrease in hesistance and increase in production can be achieved the ridding of this mental barrier
            is worked on. <![CDATA[<br/>]]> <![CDATA[<br/>]]>
            Doubles Knight Idle Revenue
        </flavor>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
        <name>Goblin Metallurgy</name>
        <flavor>
            The integration of Goblin Metallurgy in the armor of your own army can be useful. Remember... Good people learn from their mistakes,
            great people learn from their enemies. <![CDATA[<br/>]]> <![CDATA[<br/>]]>
            +1 Armor for your entire army
        </flavor>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
        <name>Arcane Static Dampening</name>
        <flavor>
            I am gonna spare you the technical jargon. Basically "static" refers to how a trap is stationary, "Arcane" means it is an Arcane Trap
            in question. (You don't have to know what Dampening is, just knows that it makes the spell more potent). <![CDATA[<br/>]]><![CDATA[<br/>]]>
            Doubles Arcane Trap damage
        </flavor>
    </Upgrade>
</Upgrades>