<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<doc>
<Upgrades>
    <Upgrade>
        <name>Fundamental Skin Science</name>
        <flavor>
            The skin of any organism can be transmuted into bronze by soaking it with water and then wringing it in a 41-43 degrees celcius
            enviromnent for 399 seconds.<![CDATA[<br/>]]><![CDATA[<br/>]]>
            +1 Bronze for every kill, even the idle kills
        </flavor>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
        <name>Blood Spear Fishing</name>
        <flavor>
            Out of the approximately 2791741.5 species of fish (Yes... there are several half-fishes), thousands of them are attracted
            to blood. Blood is good bait but it can be dangerous to have carnivorous animals know where you are.
            Blood Spear Fishing' is like a fishing-martial-art that makes using Blood safe in fishing. <![CDATA[<br/>]]><![CDATA[<br/>]]>
            Doubles Spearman Idle Revenue
        </flavor>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
        <name>Whetfish Ichthyology</name>
        <flavor>
            The Whetfish is a very common species, many can find it... few can use it. The magical scales and saliva of the fish can either
            harden solids or empower other magical sources. As you can already tell it is used to make weapons stronger
            ,hence its name which is derived from the 'whetstone' (And yes... the picture in the icon is an annotated
            Diagram of the fish). <![CDATA[<br/>]]><![CDATA[<br/>]]>
            +1 Attack for all Weapons
        </flavor>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
        <name>Blood Spear Fishing II</name>
        <flavor>
            More training means more skill, more skill allows more blood, more blood means more fish. <![CDATA[<br/>]]><![CDATA[<br/>]]>
            Doubles Spearman Idle Revenue
        </flavor>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
        <name>Swordsman Tracking</name>
        <flavor>
            Unlike Knights, Generic Swordsman are not trained how to track game. They are instead trained for armed combat. Coming from mediocre
            comes with the restriction of only having the liberty of learning one trade. In this case direct combat. <![CDATA[<br/>]]><![CDATA[<br/>]]>
            Doubles Swordsman Idle Revenue
        </flavor>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
        <name>Early Desensitization</name>
        <flavor>
            Knights are inherently sensitive to killing innocent creatures, this blatantly pointless world view prevents them from reaching
            their full hunting potential. A decrease in hesistance and increase in production can be achieved the ridding of this mental barrier
            is worked on. <![CDATA[<br/>]]> <![CDATA[<br/>]]>
            Doubles Knight Idle Revenue
        </flavor>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
        <name>Goblin Metallurgy</name>
        <flavor>
            The integration of Goblin Metallurgy in the armor of your own army can be useful. Remember... Good people learn from their mistakes,
            great people learn from their enemies. <![CDATA[<br/>]]> <![CDATA[<br/>]]>
            +1 Armor for your entire army
        </flavor>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
        <name>Arcane Static Dampening</name>
        <flavor>
            I am gonna spare you the technical jargon. Basically "static" refers to how a trap is stationary, "Arcane" means it is an Arcane Trap
            in question. (You don't have to know what Dampening is, just knows that it makes the spell more potent). <![CDATA[<br/>]]><![CDATA[<br/>]]>
            Doubles Arcane Trap damage
        </flavor>
    </Upgrade>
</Upgrades>
<Foes>
    <Foe>
        <name>Generic Goblin</name>
        <flavor>
            Generic Goblins are normally passive and weak. These guys are an ideal first enemy.
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
    <Foe>
        <name>Generic Imp</name>
        <flavor>
            Generic Imps are far stronger than the average man, Fun Fact: A Generic Imp on average can benchpress 2.32 tonnes. However for all their
            superior strength, they can be overcome by an organized number of hunters.
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
    <Foe>
        <name>Generic Snake</name>
        <flavor>
            These Snakes have a sturdy carpace capable of withstanding sharp Iron weapons without a scratch. It is important to fight these creatures
            using blunt force when you have low-grade equipment. As sharp weapons weapons of low-grade will do no harm to them.
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
    <Foe>
        <name>Killer Goblin Novice</name>
        <flavor>
            These creatures survive through eating other weaker species of goblins. And sometimes cannibalism.
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
    <Foe>
        <name>Frosty Abomination Fourth Class</name>
        <flavor>
            A cruel manifestation of arcane malevolence. Though this one is but a shade.
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
    <Foe>
        <name>Blue Imp</name>
        <flavor>
            Blue Imps are stronger than their Generic counterparts. Their blue skin is as durable as diamond.
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
    <Foe>
        <name>Regular Witch</name>
        <flavor>
            A dabbler in the Arcane, still dangerous even though inexperienced.
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
    <Foe>
        <name>Poisonous Snake</name>
        <flavor>
            These snakes have evolved to combat bigger enemies with their poisonous bite and their tough scales.
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
    <Foe>
        <name>Murderer Reaver</name>
        <flavor>
            Reavers are the mangled and corrupt souls of the recently dead, Their most dangerous ability is their lifesteal capabilty.
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
    <Foe>
        <name>Treasure Chest (Basic)</name>
        <flavor>
            A Treasure Chest! What could be inside?
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
    <Foe>
        <name>Flame Witch</name>
        <flavor>
            A Witch that dabbles specifically in fire magic, a very destructive element. Fire magic typically affects a large area and can deal a lot of damage
            in the long run if left unchecked.
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
    <Foe>
        <name>Dreadshroom</name>
        <flavor>
            A Basic skill of anyone who studies disease magic is to summon Dreadshrooms. Mushrooms that emit a deadly poison 5.2x more potent than
            Botchulinum.
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
    <Foe>
        <name>Fungalmancer</name>
        <flavor>
            Someone who indulges in a specific subset of Disease Magic, Fungalmancy. The ability to manipulate,create and spread disease-ridden fungi.
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
    <Foe>
        <name>Novice Witch</name>
        <flavor>
            These witches are not mere dabblers. They are practitioners to the higher mysteries of the Arcane.
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
    <Foe>
        <name>Chaotic Flesh</name>
        <flavor>
            A Witch that specializes in fire magic, a very destructive element. Fire magic typically affects a large area and can deal a lot of damage
            in the long run if left unchecked.
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
    <Foe>
        <name>Regular Deathspawn</name>
        <flavor>
            Spawns formed using the remains of the dead. created by Practioners of Death Magic.
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
    <Foe>
        <name>Death Knight</name>
        <flavor>
            Servants of Necromancers, corpses imbued with Death Magic. Capable of manipulating and raising the dead themselves and leech life.
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
    <Foe>
        <name>The Petty Essence of Unknown</name>
        <flavor>
            The first Essence of the unknown, weak but deadly. It is intangible and has enough power to destroy a large island with ease.
            Be careful when approaching this being.
        </flavor>
    </Foe>
</Foes>
</doc>
